

Profile

A highly motivated, confident game and account manager with exceptional multi-tasking and organizational skills.

Possessing a significant record of achievement in account management and able to quickly understand the mission, vision, and values of an organization.

Certificates

- TEFL/TESOL Certificate (Grade A)
- HSK 6+ Certificate (Chinese language)

Skills

Expert Interpersonal skills

95%

Strong analytical thinking

90%

Computer / Multi-tasking skills

90%

Communication skills

90%

Problem-solving skills

84%

Time Management skills

Interests

- Tennis / Gym
- Programming (Python)
- Web-Design / Illustration
- Self-Education

Andrii Osypenko

Account & Game Manager

Work Experience

CARRIER RELATIONS MANAGER ITIME SHANGHAI, CHINA 2012 - 2017

- manage carrier relationship with carriers, suppliers, and service partners
- coordinating calls and meetings as appropriate with carrier partners to solidify existing and develop new relationship
- develop strategic business relationships and long term business plans

SERIES ACTOR CHINESE TV MOVIE

2014 - 2015

■ acting in the Chinese movie *Blood of steal*

Link: http://m.iqiyi.com/w_19rsq0dlet.html?list=19rrkjmgxa

CARRIER SALES / ACCOUNT MANAGER Globex Telecom 2017 - 2019

- provide and negotiate freight rates to carriers and the internal sales team to ensure maximum profitability
- consistently provide service and support to carriers in an effort to build the business relationship

GAME MANAGER miHoYo Co.

2020 - 2022

- maintained a high level of customer service and resolved any issues
- manage effective customer strategies to build loyalty and to create up- and cross-selling opportunities

Education Background

2006 - 2010

UKRAINIAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY SUHOMLYNSKOHO

Applied mathematics

2019 - 2022

PYLYP ORLYK INTERNATIONAL CLASSICAL UNIVERSITY

Computer engineering